(Sheldon:)And apparently Wil wheaton's
best friend.
(Scene:)- Sheldon.
- Talk to the hand.
(Raj:)Does anyone have any words they'd like
to say about our man of the evening?
l do.
As is the tradition, l've prepared a series of
disrespectful jokes which generate humor...
(Sheldon:)...at Howard's expense.
Prepare to have your ribs tickled.
(Sheldon:)Howard, I always thought you'd be
the last one of us to ever get married...
(Sheldon:)...because you are so short
and unappealing, am I right?
(Sheldon:)Let's see here. Oh, seriously, though...
(Sheldon:)Howard, you're actually one of
the most intelligent people I know.
(Sheldon:)And that's a zinger because you're not.
l've always thought that you'd make
someone a fine husband someday.
Assuming you'd get the parts
and develop the engineering skills...
(Sheldon:)...to assemble them,
which I don't see as likely. Hot-cha!